and while we're speaking about friends i'm also the friend that puts my friend before niggas
one thousand percent so if it comes to a girl's night out a girl's day out
you're gonna have to wait till we're finished bud
this right here is not heralded enough i lost a whole friend from college who i thought was
literally like one of my sisters because we had dinner plans and some nigga came in from out of
town and she was like well we're gonna spend the whole day so can we reschedule and i was like i
done moved my schedule so we could have the dinner why why i got to move now because this man wanted
to move in and she said well i mean are you like mad i'm like yeah i'm mad i am angry you literally
telling me that we have to stop our dinner because this man has arrived and he ain't even your man
and you know what y'all she was like well i mean you can come to dinner with us i need everybody to
have more respect for themselves and for the folks in their circle because at the end of the day i was
there before that man and i would have been there after that man but instead you centered that man
and that man didn't even mean nothing let me also add she stopped talking to me because she was upset
that i was angry about that let me also add that if he was really bad about it righty righty he would
have been like well i'm gonna just rock with you for all 24 except for two so i'm gonna have a strong
22 hours with you that's how you do it y'all being a good villager is not about simply just being
generous which is giving when you have surplus but sharing finding within what you have to spread
amongst who you have someone said that they want more content like this from me and if you want
these types of takes where i'm talking about life well you can join my patreon i'll see you there for
five dollars a month support a real one
um
you